[Music] So, let's see
where Bajhang stock is,
due to the news, we are seeing news.
What should be the action, your reaction will be told.
Santosh ji will tell the news and
you will decide what should be the strategy on that stock.
After listening to all the analysis, let's
take the company one by one and today is the day of the
fourth quarter.
Fourth quarter result
updates are coming for most of the stocks and due to this, momentum is being
seen. First of all, let's talk about
Just Dial. The results of Just Dial have been
quite excellent, better than expected. The
profit of the company in the fourth quarter has
increased by almost 358 percent and it has increased to
around Rs 1.74 crore.
We have also seen an increase of around Rs 1.25 in the income
and it has been Rs
27.3 crore. Let us tell you that the
company has earned around Rs
111.6 crore in Bitta. So these are all the reasons
due to which the stock is in great momentum today. The
number of new customer visits in the fourth quarter is  17.11 crores,
so all these figures are
seen going in favor of the company and due to good
results, a good rally was being seen
in the stock. When we made the news, it was
around 10-11 and now it has gone up to
14, the share has reached 117, now this
rally of ₹1 is seen coming here.
Sir, the numbers came, the numbers were quite impressive
and the effect of the excellent results is
also being seen in the excellent share price. What will be your advice
now, what should be done
regarding Just Dial, what will be your advice for those who have it and those who are
looking to make a new purchase,
so Vipul ji, let me remind you that as far as I
remember, to buy Just Dial, we have told you on your channel that around 800-850,
you should keep it for a long
term. Now the
rationale we gave for keeping it was
that the company has a lot of cash lying with it,
more than 3000 crores, which is  At that time,
I believe that
its market cap was around Rs 7500 crore, which has now increased to Rs 8700
crore. At that time, the company had cash of more than Rs 3000 crore
in its balance sheet,
due to which we felt that this is being
kept as an investment in the company,
which will be very good and the profit will be quite
good. I think that holding it is still a good thing.
I see good value in the company.
Since the parentage is Reliance, I also
feel that there could be big plans here. The
investments that are lying around
may be for some acquisition in the future. So, the
advice would be to hold it. Not at these levels,
but if the collection is stable
at around 10-15, then you can add it. If the returns fall from 10 to 12-15, you can make a
fresh entry.
Otherwise, the advice would be to hold it for now.
Let's move ahead and bring the next company
on the screen. And that
is Indust Tower, on which many of our viewers have
asked questions.  The question was from Sunil Bish sahab,
he is from Mumbai, he is saying that whenever I was
thinking of buying, but there has been no
decline on every fall. The news
here is that the statement that came today
from Indust Tower is that the company is
hopeful that Vodafone-Idea will repay
its entire debt after the FPO. Yes, let me
tell you that there is a considerable amount
of debt on the company here. The
company is expecting repayment of this entire debt after the FPO.
And the total
debt on the company, please bring that on the screen as well.
Vodafone-Idea has a debt of around 000 crores and we will
discuss it in a while. There are other IPOs
in the segment as to what should happen, what should be the
strategy and due to this, today
we are seeing a
great move in Indust Tower. When we made the news, we were seeing
strength around 4.25
and now it is still strong at 45.
Price of 348 Sir,
what is the meaning of the statement given today because the
company is hopeful that
all its debts will be cleared in one go
and the company will
get a good amount for expansion. How are you looking at this news
Vipul ji, I would like to say that it is said that
people live on hope, so there is hope,
now everything is based on hope, but if you
look at the IPO and the money raised by the company in the IPO, the
company has not
mentioned anywhere that it will give the money to Indust Tower, it is
definitely possible that their business may improve
because the company will buy equipment worth Rs 12,000 crore, the
company will give them the
government's dues of around Rs 2,000 crore of DoT, which is the
Department of Telecommunications,
about Rs 00 crore, so the
matter of Indust Tower will come up when their business
operations start improving, so
okay, it has increased and
if you look at the business of Indust Tower, it is a tower rental
business and I think that this  There is a gain
here, you should not think of taking it
because this is a business model which is like fixed income,
rental income comes, like when we
buy a house and rent it out, the
income that comes from it is not very high,
no it is even less than the bank interest, so it is definitely true
that they have got this hope that if
their business does well then the outstanding amount of around Rs 7000 crore will
come to their company,
so I would not advise that you should
take it at this place, so
let's leave this advice here and bring the
next company that comes and
see what news has come here,
let's bring the share of Brigade Enterprise on the screen
and here also let me
tell you that the numbers have come for FY24 and Q4, the
pre-sales booking in FY24 has been the
highest on record and it has
increased to 46,013 crore,
only pre-sales advance booking of
more than Rs 6000 crore has been seen in the fourth quarter within 524
Pre-sales booking of Rs 2243 crore has been seen here,
so the pre-sale numbers are coming out quite
encouraging and very encouraging
for Brigade Enterprises and
due to this today we are seeing that there is
good momentum in the company's shares and let me
tell you that NT Stock Broking has
now increased the target on the company to
1439, so these are all the developments
due to which a good
momentum is being seen in the stock, a jump of half a point from 5 was
seen when we
made the news, if we look at it now, the price that is being seen is
1023, right now there is strength around 3,
how is Brigade Enterprises looking,
sir, do you see any possibilities here,
see, possibilities are there in the entire sector,
if you see, there is a huge potential in all the retail companies, house building companies,
housing companies,
because
we call them roti kapda aur makaan and these are the
basic necessities of a man
and whenever a man earns money, as
in India,  Per capita income is increasing, so
bread means food and drink, after that
how we dress and after that
how we buy good houses and good cars, so
it is being said that people ride the wave of the economy,
and all these companies
in this sector benefit from it, and
this company is also not untouched. We are seeing
that
their order books are continuously being sold,
inventory is decreasing, so these
things are quite good,
these things will continue in the coming days as well. Definitely, there will be
growth, but all my favorite
companies are slightly larger companies, relatively
larger ones are Oye Realty, Prestige
Real Estate, DLF, we are seeing
that at least from the safety of
capital point of view, it looks quite good. Let's move
ahead and bring the next company
on the screen, Angel
One. When we saw the numbers coming in, they were
quite encouraging, and now that is being reflected in the
company's final results as well.  The
numbers released by the company in the middle were quite good.
In the fourth quarter, the company's profit has
increased to around 257 per cent. There has been an increase of 64.4 per cent in the income
and it is increasing to ₹
57.3 crore. If we talk about EBITDA, then it has
seen an increase of 37 per cent and
it is increasing to ₹529 crore. So,
due to the excellent results, the stock was
seeing a rise of more than 2 per cent.
If we look at the initial trading session, the
strength that was there here has now been
lost. This stock has slipped from the upper levels. It has risen
very fast. Now it is
operating with a decline of half a percent.
Angel One Sir, the numbers were fine. What happened? There is
sale news in the stock. Sometimes things are such that the
market is understanding these things
because if you see, a bull market is going on
and the
direct beneficiary of the bull market is the exchange and
after that, the broker on the exchange and all the
listed brokers have us as an
opportunity investor.  People have it
that we can give there, like
today also the results of ICICI Securities are going to come, you will
see it there, but
broadly if you look at the turnover on the exchange, the
biggest gain from it is from
Angel One among the listed companies because they have gained a
good market share
in the coming past several months or years. The
company is good, the valuation is also reasonable. There is
only one fear that you should have
in your mind that whenever the bull market ends
or becomes bearish or the
market goes into correction, then their turnover
decreases because people's stock long
positions are at higher prices, then they do
not come to trade. As long as the market is up,
everyone trades, buys one thing, makes profit and
invests in another thing. This is the
general trend seen, so till then I
think this stock is good and it will continue to do well. We should
definitely look into it.
Okay sir, what happened to the market suddenly, there has been a
sharp fall
and now Nifty is trading 33 points down.  It
happened and the market has gone down very sharply,
now it is down by 26 points, there was a
small recovery in the market, but what happened,
sir, did any news reach you or
not, I am not able to see any
news, so I don't have any news on my radar,
but today, since there is an expiry, it is a
weekly expiry, so in that respect, the
market was quite negative in the morning and
after that, it became very strong and plus, now it is back
in negative, as I was telling you, there is a lot of
news these days and
you will definitely get information from this perspective, so if the
market is very fast, then you should not be bullish, it should remain a
little down, if it becomes very slow, then do
not be too bearish, that means you will have to
adopt a middle path and then you can
move, then it is possible that you can earn some money, there is
no such news that
such a big fall was seen in the market, okay, there is
no news, but yes, I
mean, stay alert, stay cautious because it is a
very volatile market, the
market is going to move according to the event, bring the next company and
see on the screen
what news is coming out there and what else.
Action is being seen in ICI
Lombard. ICI Lombard's fourth quarter
profit has increased by 19% and it has increased to 519
crores. There has been an increase of 18% in net premium
and in this, the
premium of the company has increased by 18% to 4767 crores. The
company has also given a dividend of ₹ on the share.
Many brokerage
houses have increased their targets on the stock,
due to which this stock is
coming on the radar a little more. HSBC has
set a target of 990, Magaz Stanley has given
850, CNS has said the target of 7760,
so all these international brokerage houses are
looking quite bullish
on the stock and a very good move is being seen here.
Sir, how about ICICI Lombard?
Sir, if we look at this sector and this company
today, this stock is seen in momentum since this morning. What would be the
advice now? Can we still buy it? Let's
see.  If you want to change the momentum, it seems
you can buy, but always keep in
mind that you should buy at lower levels and
their numbers are looking quite good in many numbers and in this you will see that
after Covid, their pace had slowed down a bit,
their profit growth, the growth
space had reduced, it was very less in 2022,
but if you look at the results of 2023 and 2024, they have been
quite good and
in the insurance sector,
these numbers are coming good in general insurance, in LIC
also, all the life insurance companies are
not that good, but the
numbers of this company are good. I think that if
you want to build a position anywhere, which can
bring good money, this is one of the good
stocks, among them, you should definitely look at the lower levels, okay,
not today, but yes, you
should definitely keep an eye on the lower levels
and the advice to buy there is
coming out here, it should be in your portfolio,
this is what Santosh ji believes,
let's bring today's last company on the screen of
buzzing stocks and
see what news comes out here.
So the news is coming here
about Hathway Cable and the company has
registered a profit
in the fourth quarter as compared to last year. Let me tell you that last
year the company had suffered a loss of Rs 1467 crore,
whereas this year the company is
registering a profit of Rs 34.57 crore, while the
income of the company has also increased from Rs 4459 crore to
Rs 493 crore, so
these are the current results of Hathway Cable,
very good results and if we talk about the whole year,
then in 24 hrs the profit has increased from Rs 6.37 crore to Rs
99.2 crore, so due to these better than expected
results, a rally of about % was seen
here in Hathway and
if we talk about now, the price that is being seen is being
seen, a very good rally is being
seen here, Sir, what would be
your advice regarding this,
I feel that this is the biggest thing in this space,
first of all let me tell you that this company, which is a
J company, they had bought,
in the last many years, whatever amount they have bought,
Cable distribution means the
internet that we use through cable in the office or
other places, it works, the profitability
of the company has not been that good, that is, the
condition has been very pathetic, in
terms of profitability,
even Reliance of D Speight took them in its group, in
spite of that, it has not been that good because
if you see the historical numbers, there has been a
lot of decline in earnings, the
company was in loss, gradually there was profit but it fell, then the
profit started increasing again, that means the profit is very high,
I think that overall it should be avoided,
such
sectors should be avoided, this is my opinion coming out
for you, so much about stocks for now
[Music]